typeform.com 2014-09-22

# Typeform | Privacy Policy

Typeform | Privacy policy

The user’s privacy and the confidentiality of the information that the user might obtain through or upload on the TYPEFORM Website are priorities for TYPEFORM.

**Data collected for the user’s registration**

****The user’s personal data collected through the registration form on the typeform website are incorporated to the databases of typeform in order to open an account that allows the user to make use of our services.

The data may be used to perform the services requested and to review, investigate and analyze how to improve the services provided. Typeform may also collect and analyze from visitors and users certain information regarding their use of the website. The information collected may include: website traffic volume, frequency of visits, type and time of transactions, type of browser and operating system, etc.

Typeform may collaborate with third parties in order to provide the services, in which case those third parties are required to comply with our privacy policy and any other adequate technical and organisational measures to prevent the unauthorized or illegal processing of the information and the accidental loss, destruction or impairment of the same.

Personal data are not disclosed to any third party except for providing the services you requested and for which typeform collaborates with third parties; when it is required by a competent authority in the exercise of its duties (for example in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities) or as otherwise required by law.

The user will at all times be able to exert his or her right to access, modify, cancel and oppose the processing of his or her personal data informing typeform accordingly of the matter by means of a letter sent to the address indicated in the above section “ownership of the website”.

**Information collected or contained in the typeforms created by users**

All the information that the user might obtain through or upload on the TYPEFORM Website will be subject to our privacy policy. Even though TYPEFORM operates and manages the Website, as well as the storage of the information, the user is responsible and the rightful owner of said information.

TYPEFORM is committed to:

  * Processing the information that the user might collect through or upload on the Website with the only purpose of operating and managing the platform and being able to provide the services requested by the user, not using the information for any other purpose except when expressly authorized by the user.
  * Not disclosing the information to any third party except:

  1. In those cases in which TYPEFORM collaborates with third parties in order to provide the services and, in particular, for the exploitation and operation of the platform, as well as for the storing of the information, in which case those third parties are required to comply with our privacy policy and anyother adequate technical and organisational measures to prevent the unauthorized or illegal processing of the information and the accidental loss, destruction or impairment of the same; or
  2. When it is required by a competent authority in the exercise of its duties (for example in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities); or
  3. As otherwise required by law.

  * Destroying the information or returning it to the user once the provision has been fulfilled.
  * Implementing the adequate technical and organisational measures to prevent the unauthorized or illegal processing of the information and, in particular, of the personal data, as well as the accidental loss, destruction or impairment of the same.

Modification of the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be modified, without said modification involving any prejudice to the privacy of the user or the confidentiality of the information the user might collect through or upload on the TYPEFORM Website.

The user will be properly informed and the most current version will always be available to the user on this Website.
